{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.431, 0.646], [-0.006, -0.01], [0.733, 1.1], [0.967, 1.45]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_1_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_1_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.353, 2.029], [0.727, 1.091], [0.919, 1.379], [0.756, 1.134]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_1_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_1_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.705, 1.057], [-0.412, -0.618], [-0.126, -0.189], [1.152, 1.728]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_9_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_9_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.089, -0.133], [0.522, 0.783], [-0.171, -0.256], [0.586, 0.879]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_9_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_9_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.544, 0.816], [0.114, 0.17], [0.554, 0.831], [0.083, 0.124]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_18_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_18_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.506, 0.759], [0.665, 0.997], [-0.202, -0.304], [1.115, 1.672]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_18_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_18_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.576, 0.863], [0.5, 0.75], [0.114, 0.171], [0.014, 0.022]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_20_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_20_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.349, -0.523], [0.064, 0.096], [0.49, 0.735], [0.517, 0.776]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_20_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_20_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.079, 0.118], [0.566, 0.849], [1.276, 1.915], [0.649, 0.974]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_21_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_21_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[1.09, 1.634], [-0.047, -0.07], [0.694, 1.04], [0.651, 0.977]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_21_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_21_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.62, 0.93], [0.907, 1.361], [-0.1, -0.149], [-0.672, -1.008]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_27_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_27_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.402, -0.604], [-0.175, -0.262], [-0.114, -0.172], [0.997, 1.495]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_27_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_27_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.244, 0.367], [0.043, 0.064], [0.957, 1.436], [0.257, 0.386]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_29_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_29_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.104, -0.156], [0.489, 0.733], [0.618, 0.927], [1.131, 1.696]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_29_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_29_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.604, 0.907], "wrong_answers": [[1.401, 2.102], [1.147, 1.721], [0.372, 0.559], [0.322, 0.483]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_30_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_30_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.008, 1.512], [0.196, 0.294], [0.146, 0.219], [0.257, 0.386]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_30_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_30_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.114, 0.171], [0.795, 1.193], [0.109, 0.164], [0.816, 1.224]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_30_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_30_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.2, -0.301], [0.192, 0.287], [1.537, 2.306], [-0.067, -0.1]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_30_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_30_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.1, -0.15], [0.039, 0.058], [-0.216, -0.324], [0.074, 0.112]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_32_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_32_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[-0.413, -0.619], [0.726, 1.089], [0.029, 0.044], [-0.117, -0.175]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_32_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_32_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.076, -0.114], [0.995, 1.493], [0.2, 0.301], [-0.028, -0.042]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_33_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_33_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.085, 0.127], [1.29, 1.935], [1.044, 1.567], [0.723, 1.085]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_33_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_33_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.704, 1.056], [0.85, 1.275], [1.209, 1.814], [0.213, 0.319]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_40_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_40_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.206, -0.31], [0.076, 0.115], [0.8, 1.2], [0.679, 1.018]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_40_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_40_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.017, -0.026], [0.065, 0.097], [1.524, 2.286], [0.881, 1.322]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_42_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_42_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.75, 1.125], [0.012, 0.019], [0.774, 1.162], [0.691, 1.037]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_42_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_42_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.577, 0.866], [0.091, 0.137], [0.857, 1.285], [0.624, 0.936]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_44_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_44_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.089, -0.134], [0.173, 0.26], [0.534, 0.801], [0.177, 0.265]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_44_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_44_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.375, -0.563], [-0.063, -0.094], [0.422, 0.633], [0.056, 0.084]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_46_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_46_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.814, 1.221], [-0.006, -0.009], [0.196, 0.294], [0.216, 0.325]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_46_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_46_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.029, 1.543], [0.81, 1.216], [-0.81, -1.215], [0.657, 0.986]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_46_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_46_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.16, 0.241], [0.898, 1.347], [0.17, 0.255], [0.001, 0.002]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_46_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_46_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.127, -0.19], [0.878, 1.317], [-0.169, -0.253], [0.548, 0.821]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_48_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_48_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[1.238, 1.857], [-0.262, -0.393], [0.955, 1.432], [-0.351, -0.526]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_48_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_48_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.157, -0.236], [-0.09, -0.135], [0.159, 0.238], [-0.145, -0.218]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.204, -0.306], [0.819, 1.228], [0.925, 1.387], [0.049, 0.074]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.553, 0.829], [0.46, 0.69], [0.584, 0.876], [0.486, 0.728]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_53_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_53_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.971, 1.456], [0.973, 1.46], [-0.089, -0.134], [-0.357, -0.536]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_53_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_53_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.748, 1.122], [0.076, 0.114], [0.602, 0.903], [0.959, 1.438]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_60_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_60_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.222, 0.333], [-0.077, -0.115], [0.014, 0.021], [0.143, 0.214]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_60_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_60_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.416, 0.625], [-0.289, -0.433], [0.732, 1.098], [0.421, 0.631]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_62_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_62_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.699, 1.049], [-0.163, -0.245], [0.222, 0.333], [0.728, 1.092]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_62_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_62_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.095, 0.143], [1.172, 1.758], [0.323, 0.485], [1.316, 1.974]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_67_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_67_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[1.047, 1.57], [0.948, 1.422], [1.165, 1.748], [0.909, 1.363]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_67_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_67_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.198, -0.297], [-0.219, -0.328], [0.653, 0.979], [0.133, 0.199]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.774, -1.16], [-0.248, -0.372], [0.788, 1.182], [0.715, 1.072]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.8, 1.2], [0.102, 0.152], [0.97, 1.454], [0.858, 1.288]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.017, -0.025], [0.565, 0.847], [0.792, 1.188], [0.937, 1.406]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_69_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.732, 1.097], [0.116, 0.175], [0.093, 0.14], [0.675, 1.013]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_70_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_70_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.096, 0.144], [0.843, 1.264], [-0.138, -0.207], [-0.011, -0.016]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_70_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_70_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.583, 0.875], [0.026, 0.039], [0.56, 0.839], [1.078, 1.617]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_71_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_71_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.174, 0.261], [-0.081, -0.122], [0.739, 1.108], [0.534, 0.8]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_71_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_71_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.039, 0.059], [-0.02, -0.03], [0.084, 0.126], [0.04, 0.06]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_74_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_74_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.107, 0.161], [1.095, 1.642], [-0.11, -0.165], [0.718, 1.076]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_74_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_74_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.858, 1.287], [0.733, 1.099], [-0.039, -0.059], [0.141, 0.212]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_76_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_76_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.001, -0.002], [-0.318, -0.478], [-0.446, -0.669], [1.248, 1.872]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_76_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_76_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.149, 1.724], [1.053, 1.58], [0.236, 0.354], [0.742, 1.113]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_77_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_77_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.681, 1.022], [0.02, 0.029], [0.518, 0.777], [0.691, 1.036]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_77_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_77_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.028, 0.043], [-0.1, -0.15], [-0.24, -0.36], [0.481, 0.721]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_78_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_78_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.119, 0.178], [0.196, 0.293], [0.828, 1.242], [0.056, 0.085]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_78_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_78_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.736, 1.104], [0.461, 0.691], [0.491, 0.736], [0.085, 0.127]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.769, 1.154], [-0.038, -0.057], [0.071, 0.107], [0.873, 1.31]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[0.884, 1.326], [0.92, 1.38], [1.315, 1.973], [0.258, 0.387]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.233, 0.349], [0.111, 0.167], [0.312, 0.468], [0.124, 0.187]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_82_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.169, 0.253], [0.822, 1.233], [0.056, 0.084], [0.275, 0.412]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_83_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_83_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.953, 1.43], [0.967, 1.451], [0.611, 0.917], [0.717, 1.075]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_83_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_83_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.69, 1.035], [0.463, 0.695], [0.132, 0.198], [0.623, 0.935]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.066, 0.099], [0.584, 0.877], [0.171, 0.257], [0.148, 0.222]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.065, 0.097], [0.163, 0.245], [0.169, 0.254], [0.277, 0.415]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.797, 1.196], [-0.073, -0.109], [0.297, 0.446], [0.978, 1.467]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_88_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.909, 1.364], [0.994, 1.491], [0.275, 0.413], [1.339, 2.009]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_92_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_92_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.569, 0.853], "wrong_answers": [[1.007, 1.51], [1.398, 2.097], [1.2, 1.8], [0.373, 0.56]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_92_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_92_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.063, 0.095], [-0.091, -0.137], [1.335, 2.002], [0.06, 0.091]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_92_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_92_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.328, 0.493], [0.262, 0.393], [1.225, 1.837], [0.071, 0.106]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_92_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_92_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[1.097, 1.646], [0.647, 0.97], [0.572, 0.858], [-0.033, -0.05]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_93_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_93_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.332, -0.499], [0.545, 0.818], [0.618, 0.927], [0.709, 1.064]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_93_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_93_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.654, 0.981], [0.654, 0.981], [1.067, 1.601], [-0.305, -0.457]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_98_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_98_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.994, 1.491], [0.793, 1.189], [0.051, 0.077], [0.694, 1.041]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_98_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_98_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.156, 0.234], [0.142, 0.212], [0.116, 0.174], [-0.309, -0.464]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.648, 0.973], [-0.049, -0.073], [0.102, 0.154], [0.598, 0.897]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.935, 1.402], [1.21, 1.815], [-0.013, -0.02], [0.199, 0.298]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.278, 0.416], [0.094, 0.142], [0.303, 0.454], [1.376, 2.064]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.182, 1.772], [0.088, 0.132], [0.094, 0.141], [0.597, 0.896]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_102_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_102_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.811, 1.216], [0.214, 0.32], [0.744, 1.116], [-0.089, -0.133]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_102_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_102_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.332, -0.499], [0.786, 1.179], [-0.436, -0.655], [-0.621, -0.932]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_103_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_103_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.044, -0.065], [0.137, 0.205], [-0.211, -0.317], [0.099, 0.149]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_103_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_103_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.918, 1.377], [0.938, 1.407], [0.99, 1.484], [0.314, 0.471]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_105_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_105_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.622, 0.933], "wrong_answers": [[0.381, 0.571], [0.205, 0.308], [1.174, 1.762], [1.093, 1.64]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_105_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_105_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.182, 0.274], [1.398, 2.096], [1.032, 1.547], [0.49, 0.734]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_107_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_107_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.018, -0.027], [-0.038, -0.056], [0.204, 0.306], [0.939, 1.408]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_107_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_107_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.087, 0.131], [0.559, 0.838], [0.13, 0.196], [0.404, 0.606]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_108_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_108_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[-0.325, -0.487], [-0.451, -0.676], [0.105, 0.158], [0.026, 0.039]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_108_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_108_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[1.093, 1.64], [0.692, 1.038], [0.54, 0.81], [1.021, 1.531]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.913, 1.37], [1.029, 1.544], [1.469, 2.203], [-0.056, -0.084]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.625, 0.938], [0.147, 0.221], [0.535, 0.802], [0.57, 0.855]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.083, 0.124], [0.103, 0.155], [0.623, 0.935], [-0.027, -0.041]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_111_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.316, 0.474], [-0.243, -0.364], [1.2, 1.8], [0.913, 1.369]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_114_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_114_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.604, 0.907], "wrong_answers": [[1.234, 1.851], [1.063, 1.595], [0.331, 0.496], [-0.13, -0.196]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_114_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_114_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.29, 0.434], [1.291, 1.937], [0.959, 1.439], [-0.345, -0.517]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_118_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_118_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.168, 0.253], [0.06, 0.089], [0.747, 1.12], [0.736, 1.104]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_118_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_118_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.151, 1.727], [0.478, 0.716], [0.535, 0.802], [0.556, 0.834]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_121_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_121_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.341, 2.011], [0.832, 1.248], [0.943, 1.414], [0.75, 1.124]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_121_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_121_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.635, 0.952], [0.712, 1.068], [0.985, 1.478], [0.957, 1.435]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_123_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_123_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.671, 1.007], [-0.252, -0.378], [0.483, 0.724], [0.63, 0.945]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_123_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_123_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.061, 0.092], [-0.173, -0.26], [-0.129, -0.193], [0.048, 0.073]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_129_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_129_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.755, 1.133], [0.159, 0.238], [0.528, 0.792], [0.591, 0.887]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_129_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_129_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.172, 0.258], [0.161, 0.241], [0.431, 0.646], [0.552, 0.828]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_135_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_135_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.426, -0.639], [-0.714, -1.071], [-0.079, -0.119], [0.726, 1.089]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_135_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_135_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.176, 0.264], [0.055, 0.082], [0.969, 1.454], [-0.007, -0.011]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_141_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_141_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.314, -0.472], [0.074, 0.11], [0.114, 0.172], [0.992, 1.489]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_141_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_141_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[1.15, 1.725], [0.593, 0.89], [0.57, 0.855], [1.469, 2.203]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_142_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_142_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.604, 0.905], [-0.196, -0.294], [1.046, 1.569], [0.523, 0.784]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_142_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_142_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.02, -0.03], [0.445, 0.668], [1.255, 1.883], [0.051, 0.077]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_143_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_143_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.269, 1.904], [-0.341, -0.512], [1.22, 1.83], [0.428, 0.642]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_143_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_143_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.227, 1.841], [0.288, 0.431], [0.083, 0.125], [-0.139, -0.209]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.604, 0.907], "wrong_answers": [[1.326, 1.99], [0.928, 1.392], [1.053, 1.58], [-0.133, -0.199]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.125, -0.187], [0.974, 1.461], [0.765, 1.148], [0.757, 1.136]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.541, 0.812], [0.528, 0.792], [-0.227, -0.341], [0.151, 0.226]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.569, 0.853], "wrong_answers": [[1.302, 1.953], [0.867, 1.3], [0.057, 0.086], [0.067, 0.1]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_151_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_151_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[1.038, 1.557], [0.996, 1.494], [0.123, 0.184], [0.22, 0.329]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_151_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_151_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.472, 0.707], [0.64, 0.96], [0.716, 1.073], [-0.013, -0.02]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_153_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_153_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[1.031, 1.547], [0.582, 0.873], [0.692, 1.038], [0.726, 1.089]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_153_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_153_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.959, 1.438], [0.887, 1.331], [0.814, 1.221], [0.785, 1.177]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_156_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_156_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.668, 1.001], [0.178, 0.267], [-0.163, -0.244], [-0.456, -0.685]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_156_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_156_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.151, 0.227], [0.608, 0.911], [1.021, 1.531], [-0.111, -0.166]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_157_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_157_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.035, 0.052], [-0.377, -0.565], [-0.191, -0.286], [0.528, 0.792]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_157_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_157_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.224, 0.336], [1.492, 2.238], [0.942, 1.413], [1.348, 2.023]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_159_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_159_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.615, 0.922], [0.259, 0.389], [0.119, 0.179], [1.019, 1.529]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_159_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_159_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.211, -0.316], [0.187, 0.28], [0.098, 0.147], [0.083, 0.124]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_160_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_160_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.112, -0.168], [0.647, 0.971], [-0.025, -0.037], [-0.239, -0.359]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_160_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_160_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.043, -0.065], [0.186, 0.28], [0.691, 1.037], [0.058, 0.086]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_162_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_162_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[-0.057, -0.085], [1.213, 1.819], [-0.032, -0.047], [-0.52, -0.779]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_162_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_162_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.949, 1.424], [0.05, 0.075], [0.589, 0.884], [0.613, 0.92]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.099, -0.148], [0.003, 0.005], [0.375, 0.563], [0.68, 1.021]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.8, 1.2], [0.922, 1.383], [0.817, 1.226], [0.821, 1.232]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.172, 0.258], [0.235, 0.352], [0.854, 1.282], [-0.228, -0.342]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_164_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.758, 1.138], [-0.224, -0.336], [0.655, 0.983], [0.211, 0.316]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_168_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_168_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.793, 1.189], [0.262, 0.393], [0.951, 1.426], [0.126, 0.189]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_168_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_168_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.083, 0.125], [-0.098, -0.146], [0.179, 0.269], [0.109, 0.163]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_169_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_169_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[1.009, 1.514], [0.75, 1.126], [1.054, 1.58], [0.882, 1.324]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_169_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_169_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.107, -0.16], [0.593, 0.889], [0.444, 0.667], [0.45, 0.676]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_172_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_172_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.081, 0.122], [-0.197, -0.296], [0.843, 1.264], [0.48, 0.72]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_172_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_172_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.826, 1.239], [0.459, 0.689], [0.75, 1.125], [0.123, 0.185]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.088, 1.633], [-0.217, -0.326], [0.814, 1.221], [0.682, 1.024]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.957, 1.435], [0.253, 0.38], [0.12, 0.18], [0.898, 1.347]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_178_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_178_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.006, -0.009], [0.663, 0.994], [0.703, 1.055], [-0.138, -0.207]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_178_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_178_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.585, 0.877], [0.006, 0.009], [0.992, 1.488], [0.864, 1.296]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_179_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_179_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.891, 1.337], [0.593, 0.89], [-0.046, -0.069], [0.642, 0.963]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_179_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_179_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.072, 1.609], [-0.147, -0.22], [0.143, 0.214], [0.781, 1.171]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_179_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_179_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.707, 1.061], [-0.35, -0.526], [0.694, 1.041], [1.138, 1.707]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_179_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_179_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.124, 0.186], [0.04, 0.06], [1.102, 1.652], [1.066, 1.599]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_181_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_181_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.941, 1.412], [0.991, 1.487], [1.26, 1.889], [0.201, 0.302]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_181_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_181_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.311, -0.467], [0.034, 0.05], [0.053, 0.079], [0.871, 1.306]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_196_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_196_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.717, 1.076], [0.519, 0.778], [1.352, 2.028], [-0.37, -0.555]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_196_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_196_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.76, 1.14], [0.566, 0.849], [-0.17, -0.256], [-0.629, -0.944]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.483, 0.725], [0.615, 0.923], [-0.194, -0.291], [0.631, 0.947]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[-0.096, -0.145], [0.284, 0.426], [0.592, 0.888], [-0.287, -0.43]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[-0.478, -0.718], [0.953, 1.429], [0.354, 0.531], [0.535, 0.802]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_197_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.622, 0.934], [0.698, 1.047], [1.124, 1.686], [1.242, 1.863]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_198_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_198_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[1.029, 1.544], [1.051, 1.576], [0.03, 0.045], [0.196, 0.294]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_198_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_198_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.406, 0.609], [-0.15, -0.225], [0.588, 0.882], [-0.6, -0.9]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_203_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_203_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.279, 1.918], [0.466, 0.699], [0.569, 0.853], [-0.056, -0.084]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_203_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_203_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[0.167, 0.251], [0.334, 0.501], [1.325, 1.987], [0.353, 0.529]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_204_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_204_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.895, 1.343], [1.148, 1.721], [0.099, 0.148], [0.183, 0.274]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_204_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_204_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.544, 0.816], [-0.223, -0.334], [0.568, 0.852], [0.642, 0.963]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_206_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_206_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.746, 1.119], [0.587, 0.881], [-0.114, -0.172], [0.036, 0.054]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_206_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_206_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.196, 0.294], [0.823, 1.235], [1.291, 1.936], [0.061, 0.091]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.986, 1.479], [0.014, 0.021], [-0.277, -0.415], [0.164, 0.246]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.971, 1.457], [0.88, 1.321], [0.118, 0.177], [0.037, 0.055]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.282, 0.423], [-0.43, -0.645], [1.031, 1.547], [0.869, 1.303]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.604, 0.905], [0.652, 0.979], [-0.852, -1.277], [0.897, 1.345]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_207_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_207_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.313, -0.469], [0.774, 1.16], [-0.107, -0.16], [0.629, 0.944]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_207_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_207_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.588, 0.882], [0.133, 0.199], [-0.375, -0.563], [-0.206, -0.309]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_208_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_208_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.803, 1.205], [-0.06, -0.089], [0.582, 0.873], [-0.188, -0.281]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_208_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_208_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.713, -1.07], [0.713, 1.069], [-0.034, -0.051], [0.556, 0.833]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.097, 0.145], [0.673, 1.009], [0.097, 0.145], [-0.203, -0.304]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.487, 0.73], [-0.624, -0.936], [-0.601, -0.901], [0.618, 0.926]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.045, 1.568], [0.172, 0.259], [0.95, 1.425], [0.987, 1.481]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_214_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.569, 0.853], "wrong_answers": [[0.236, 0.355], [0.949, 1.424], [1.02, 1.53], [1.004, 1.506]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_215_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_215_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[-0.042, -0.063], [0.298, 0.447], [0.35, 0.525], [1.076, 1.613]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_215_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_215_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.105, 1.657], [0.633, 0.95], [0.533, 0.799], [-0.042, -0.064]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[1.235, 1.853], [1.179, 1.768], [1.328, 1.992], [0.73, 1.095]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.733, 1.099], [0.048, 0.072], [1.471, 2.207], [1.123, 1.684]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.011, -0.017], [0.498, 0.747], [-0.017, -0.026], [0.977, 1.466]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.142, 0.213], "wrong_answers": [[0.296, 0.444], [-0.1, -0.151], [0.453, 0.68], [0.588, 0.882]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_217_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_217_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.889, 1.333], [1.379, 2.069], [0.766, 1.148], [0.116, 0.175]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_217_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_217_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.314, 0.471], [0.048, 0.073], [1.392, 2.088], [0.858, 1.287]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_217_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_217_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.789, 1.183], [0.74, 1.11], [-0.227, -0.34], [0.204, 0.307]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_217_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_217_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.714, 1.071], [0.005, 0.008], [1.236, 1.854], [-0.024, -0.035]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_219_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_219_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.13, 0.195], [0.032, 0.048], [-0.139, -0.209], [0.055, 0.082]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_219_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_219_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.657, 0.986], [-0.448, -0.672], [0.413, 0.619], [0.9, 1.35]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_222_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_222_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.693, 1.039], [0.466, 0.7], [0.153, 0.23], [-0.004, -0.006]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_222_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_222_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.523, 0.785], [0.609, 0.913], [0.577, 0.865], [-0.039, -0.059]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_223_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_223_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.345, 0.517], [0.616, 0.923], [0.368, 0.553], [0.55, 0.825]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_223_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_223_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.154, 0.23], [0.836, 1.253], [0.833, 1.25], [0.512, 0.767]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_224_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_224_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.72, 1.081], [0.978, 1.467], [0.107, 0.161], [0.799, 1.198]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_224_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_224_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.015, 0.023], [0.545, 0.817], [-0.024, -0.037], [0.667, 1.001]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_224_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_224_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.634, 0.951], [1.043, 1.565], [1.307, 1.961], [0.6, 0.901]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_224_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_224_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.816, 1.224], [0.895, 1.343], [-0.114, -0.171], [0.594, 0.892]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_225_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_225_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.037, 0.056], [0.869, 1.303], [-0.038, -0.057], [-0.096, -0.144]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_225_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_225_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[1.343, 2.014], [0.062, 0.093], [0.088, 0.132], [0.845, 1.268]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_227_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_227_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.348, 0.522], [0.669, 1.004], [-0.2, -0.3], [0.306, 0.459]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_227_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_227_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.613, 0.92], [1.062, 1.593], [0.671, 1.007], [0.672, 1.008]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_229_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_229_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.069, 0.104], [0.344, 0.516], [-0.4, -0.599], [1.038, 1.556]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_229_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_229_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.79, 1.185], [0.568, 0.851], [0.527, 0.791], [-0.397, -0.595]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_233_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_233_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.94, 1.41], [0.618, 0.927], [-0.182, -0.273], [0.604, 0.906]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_233_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_233_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.209, 0.313], [0.652, 0.978], [0.776, 1.164], [0.163, 0.245]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_234_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_234_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.185, 0.278], [0.239, 0.358], [-0.02, -0.029], [0.276, 0.414]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_234_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_234_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.106, 0.159], [0.614, 0.921], [0.063, 0.095], [0.619, 0.928]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[1.178, 1.768], [0.757, 1.135], [-0.177, -0.265], [1.189, 1.784]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.164, 1.746], [0.861, 1.292], [0.519, 0.779], [0.135, 0.203]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[0.353, 0.53], [0.859, 1.288], [0.093, 0.139], [0.537, 0.805]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.004, -0.006], [0.636, 0.954], [0.823, 1.234], [0.821, 1.232]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.047, 0.071], [0.796, 1.193], [0.104, 0.156], [0.154, 0.23]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.006, -0.01], [0.07, 0.105], [-0.261, -0.391], [1.073, 1.609]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.051, 0.076], [0.769, 1.154], [0.699, 1.048], [0.161, 0.241]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.202, -0.303], [0.879, 1.319], [-0.013, -0.02], [0.112, 0.168]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_237_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_237_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.657, 0.986], [0.424, 0.637], [0.376, 0.563], [0.562, 0.844]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_237_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_237_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.105, 0.157], [0.209, 0.314], [0.206, 0.309], [0.677, 1.015]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_239_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_239_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.809, 1.213], [-0.372, -0.557], [0.245, 0.367], [-0.018, -0.027]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_239_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_239_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.723, 1.085], [-0.029, -0.044], [0.94, 1.41], [0.186, 0.279]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_245_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_245_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.794, 1.191], [0.67, 1.005], [1.001, 1.502], [1.042, 1.562]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_245_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_245_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[-0.04, -0.06], [-0.355, -0.532], [0.209, 0.313], [0.679, 1.018]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_248_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_248_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.648, 0.972], [0.682, 1.023], [0.18, 0.27], [-0.332, -0.499]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_248_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_248_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[1.027, 1.54], [0.729, 1.094], [1.857, 2.785], [0.738, 1.107]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_252_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_252_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.172, 1.758], [0.027, 0.041], [0.865, 1.297], [0.048, 0.072]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_252_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_252_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[1.084, 1.627], [1.11, 1.665], [0.95, 1.425], [0.23, 0.345]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_252_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_252_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.828, 1.243], [1.386, 2.079], [0.902, 1.353], [1.002, 1.503]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_252_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_252_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[0.346, 0.519], [0.634, 0.952], [-0.081, -0.122], [0.269, 0.404]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_257_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_257_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.581, 0.872], [-0.224, -0.336], [-0.1, -0.151], [0.944, 1.416]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_257_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_257_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.532, -0.798], [0.568, 0.853], [0.501, 0.751], [0.001, 0.002]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_263_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_263_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.153, -0.23], [0.474, 0.711], [0.684, 1.026], [0.155, 0.232]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_263_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_263_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.163, -0.244], [0.409, 0.613], [-0.043, -0.065], [0.277, 0.415]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_266_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_266_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[-0.043, -0.064], [0.097, 0.145], [0.577, 0.866], [0.57, 0.855]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_266_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_266_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.887, 1.33], [1.132, 1.699], [0.909, 1.364], [0.78, 1.17]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_268_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_268_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.025, -0.038], [0.704, 1.056], [0.689, 1.034], [0.614, 0.921]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_268_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_268_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.058, -0.087], [0.128, 0.193], [-0.082, -0.123], [-0.084, -0.127]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_269_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_269_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.178, -0.267], [0.844, 1.265], [0.704, 1.057], [-0.037, -0.055]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_269_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_269_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.249, -0.373], [0.536, 0.805], [-0.11, -0.165], [-0.27, -0.406]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_273_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_273_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[1.072, 1.609], [-0.218, -0.327], [0.568, 0.852], [0.048, 0.071]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_273_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_273_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.597, 0.896], [-0.544, -0.817], [0.137, 0.206], [-0.118, -0.177]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_273_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_273_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.952, 1.427], [0.874, 1.311], [0.186, 0.278], [1.413, 2.12]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_273_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_273_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.086, 1.63], [0.527, 0.791], [0.498, 0.747], [-0.116, -0.174]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_274_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_274_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.467, 0.7], [0.865, 1.298], [0.123, 0.184], [0.601, 0.901]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_274_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_274_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.663, 0.995], [0.692, 1.038], [-0.173, -0.259], [1.491, 2.237]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_274_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_274_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.173, -0.26], [0.332, 0.498], [0.863, 1.294], [-0.076, -0.114]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_274_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_274_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.262, -0.392], [0.018, 0.027], [0.483, 0.724], [1.174, 1.761]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.567, 0.851], [0.424, 0.636], [0.895, 1.343], [0.412, 0.618]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.137, 0.206], [-0.143, -0.214], [0.726, 1.089], [-0.106, -0.16]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.593, 0.89], [-0.854, -1.281], [-0.435, -0.653], [0.07, 0.105]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.198, 0.296], [0.064, 0.096], [1.476, 2.214], [0.101, 0.152]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[-0.013, -0.019], [1.242, 1.863], [0.328, 0.492], [0.833, 1.25]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_277_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.976, 1.463], [0.809, 1.213], [0.694, 1.042], [0.835, 1.252]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.169, 0.253], [0.434, 0.651], [0.777, 1.165], [0.956, 1.434]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.018, 0.026], [0.674, 1.011], [0.9, 1.351], [0.696, 1.045]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_278_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_278_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.545, 0.817], [1.194, 1.791], [0.864, 1.296], [0.709, 1.063]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_278_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_278_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.37, -0.555], [0.131, 0.197], [0.083, 0.124], [0.041, 0.061]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_280_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_280_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.417, 0.625], [0.756, 1.134], [0.492, 0.738], [0.683, 1.024]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_280_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_280_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.56, 0.84], [0.964, 1.446], [0.117, 0.175], [0.665, 0.997]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.218, -0.327], [-0.178, -0.268], [0.754, 1.131], [0.672, 1.008]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.814, 1.221], [-0.16, -0.239], [-0.216, -0.324], [1.13, 1.694]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.394, 0.591], [-0.506, -0.759], [0.897, 1.345], [0.896, 1.344]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.322, 0.482], [0.114, 0.171], [0.85, 1.275], [0.177, 0.266]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.569, 0.853], "wrong_answers": [[0.225, 0.337], [1.073, 1.609], [0.186, 0.279], [1.362, 2.043]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_288_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.555, 0.832], [0.046, 0.069], [0.819, 1.228], [-0.121, -0.182]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_289_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_289_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.368, 2.052], [0.643, 0.964], [-0.005, -0.008], [1.292, 1.939]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_289_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_289_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.25, 0.375], [0.109, 0.163], [0.155, 0.232], [1.121, 1.681]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_291_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_291_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.506, 0.759], [0.864, 1.296], [-0.078, -0.118], [0.499, 0.748]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_291_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_291_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.848, 1.272], [0.118, 0.177], [-0.246, -0.369], [0.846, 1.269]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_294_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_294_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.04, 1.56], [0.698, 1.047], [-0.192, -0.288], [0.032, 0.048]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_294_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_294_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[1.044, 1.566], [0.764, 1.146], [0.002, 0.003], [-0.162, -0.243]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_297_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_297_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[1.083, 1.624], [0.178, 0.267], [0.874, 1.312], [-0.15, -0.225]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_297_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_297_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.056, 0.084], [-0.359, -0.539], [1.217, 1.826], [0.585, 0.878]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_304_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_304_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.267, 1.901], [0.822, 1.234], [0.533, 0.8], [0.722, 1.084]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_304_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_304_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.366, -0.55], [0.194, 0.291], [0.053, 0.08], [0.733, 1.099]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_307_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_307_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.679, 1.018], [0.971, 1.457], [0.197, 0.296], [0.737, 1.106]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_307_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_307_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.945, 1.417], [0.613, 0.919], [0.649, 0.973], [0.79, 1.185]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[1.053, 1.579], [0.745, 1.118], [1.195, 1.792], [1.039, 1.558]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.776, 1.164], [0.586, 0.879], [-0.106, -0.159], [0.112, 0.167]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.699, 1.049], [0.754, 1.132], [0.147, 0.221], [0.675, 1.013]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_308_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.04, -0.06], [0.524, 0.786], [1.22, 1.83], [0.555, 0.832]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_310_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_310_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.389, -0.584], [0.892, 1.338], [1.119, 1.679], [-0.096, -0.144]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_310_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_310_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.954, 1.432], [0.7, 1.05], [0.914, 1.37], [-0.108, -0.163]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.399, 0.598], [1.027, 1.54], [0.533, 0.8], [0.459, 0.689]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.805, 1.208], [0.198, 0.297], [0.177, 0.265], [-0.014, -0.021]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_313_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_313_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.402, -0.603], [0.628, 0.942], [0.57, 0.855], [0.074, 0.11]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_313_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_313_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.302, 0.453], [0.107, 0.16], [1.036, 1.554], [0.249, 0.374]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_315_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_315_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.043, 0.065], [0.964, 1.446], [0.76, 1.139], [0.813, 1.22]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_315_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_315_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.197, 0.296], [0.632, 0.948], [-0.118, -0.176], [-0.167, -0.251]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_316_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_316_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.468, 0.701], [1.134, 1.701], [0.106, 0.159], [0.649, 0.973]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_316_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_316_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.139, 0.209], [0.086, 0.129], [-0.01, -0.015], [1.212, 1.818]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_317_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_317_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.33, 0.496], [-0.133, -0.199], [0.338, 0.507], [1.013, 1.52]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_317_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_317_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.068, 0.102], [0.141, 0.212], [0.206, 0.309], [-0.663, -0.994]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_318_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_318_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.013, 0.02], [-0.161, -0.242], [0.039, 0.058], [1.007, 1.511]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_318_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_318_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.515, 0.772], [-0.092, -0.138], [0.097, 0.146], [0.846, 1.269]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_323_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_323_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.848, 1.272], [-0.01, -0.015], [0.045, 0.068], [0.605, 0.907]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_323_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_323_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[1.116, 1.674], [0.011, 0.016], [0.88, 1.32], [0.791, 1.187]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_326_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_326_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.012, 0.019], [1.366, 2.048], [0.955, 1.432], [0.215, 0.322]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_326_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_326_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.83, 1.244], [0.136, 0.204], [1.007, 1.51], [0.725, 1.088]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_328_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_328_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.151, -0.227], [0.76, 1.141], [0.66, 0.99], [0.865, 1.297]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_328_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_328_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.888, 1.331], [1.052, 1.579], [0.98, 1.469], [1.011, 1.517]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_333_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_333_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.813, 1.219], [1.014, 1.521], [0.786, 1.178], [0.709, 1.063]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_333_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_333_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[1.303, 1.954], [0.727, 1.09], [0.648, 0.972], [-0.186, -0.279]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.118, 0.177], [-0.044, -0.067], [0.805, 1.208], [0.774, 1.16]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.747, 1.121], [0.524, 0.786], [0.591, 0.887], [0.118, 0.177]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_338_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_338_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.697, 1.046], [-0.036, -0.053], [0.025, 0.037], [0.749, 1.124]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_338_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_338_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.187, 0.281], [-0.029, -0.044], [-0.086, -0.129], [1.24, 1.86]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.695, 1.042], [0.037, 0.056], [0.617, 0.926], [0.731, 1.096]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.132, 0.198], [0.353, 0.529], [0.143, 0.214], [-0.517, -0.776]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.833, 1.249], [-0.091, -0.137], [0.776, 1.164], [-0.111, -0.166]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.818, 1.227], [0.174, 0.261], [-0.652, -0.978], [0.715, 1.073]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.17, 1.755], [1.082, 1.623], [0.075, 0.113], [0.677, 1.015]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.036, 1.554], [0.489, 0.734], [0.57, 0.855], [1.001, 1.502]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.405, 0.608], [-0.213, -0.319], [0.335, 0.502], [0.068, 0.102]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_341_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.597, 0.895], [0.141, 0.212], [0.748, 1.122], [0.678, 1.017]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_341_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_341_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.09, 0.134], [-0.603, -0.904], [0.214, 0.321], [0.043, 0.065]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_341_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_341_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.246, 0.368], [0.597, 0.895], [0.878, 1.317], [-0.145, -0.217]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.016, -0.024], [0.587, 0.88], [0.784, 1.176], [0.079, 0.118]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.529, 0.794], [-0.663, -0.995], [0.765, 1.147], [0.53, 0.795]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.179, -0.269], [0.79, 1.184], [-0.182, -0.273], [0.813, 1.219]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.032, -0.047], [0.142, 0.213], [0.79, 1.185], [1.066, 1.599]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.647, 0.97], [0.916, 1.374], [0.157, 0.236], [0.92, 1.38]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.913, 1.37], [0.991, 1.487], [0.267, 0.401], [-0.036, -0.053]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.122, 0.183], [0.098, 0.147], [0.866, 1.298], [0.066, 0.099]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.585, 0.877], [0.374, 0.561], [0.444, 0.666], [0.732, 1.098]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.505, 0.758], [0.552, 0.829], [0.641, 0.962], [-0.519, -0.779]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.567, -0.85], [-0.001, -0.002], [-0.0, -0.0], [0.658, 0.987]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_349_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_349_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.795, 1.192], [-0.039, -0.058], [0.683, 1.025], [-0.154, -0.231]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_349_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_349_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.142, 0.213], "wrong_answers": [[-0.099, -0.149], [-0.182, -0.274], [0.058, 0.087], [0.043, 0.065]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_351_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_351_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.132, 0.198], [0.978, 1.467], [-0.315, -0.473], [0.442, 0.663]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_351_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_351_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.134, 0.2], [0.139, 0.209], [-0.237, -0.355], [-0.321, -0.481]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_351_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_351_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.209, 0.313], [0.686, 1.029], [0.887, 1.33], [0.601, 0.901]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_351_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_351_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[-1.124, -1.686], [0.09, 0.135], [0.928, 1.392], [0.324, 0.486]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_352_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_352_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.532, 0.798], [0.357, 0.535], [1.052, 1.578], [0.361, 0.541]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_352_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_352_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.627, -0.941], [-0.356, -0.534], [0.91, 1.365], [0.914, 1.371]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_355_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_355_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.672, 1.008], [0.935, 1.402], [0.093, 0.139], [0.92, 1.38]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_355_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_355_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.975, 1.462], [0.024, 0.037], [0.801, 1.201], [-0.066, -0.099]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.216, -0.324], [1.219, 1.828], [-0.786, -1.179], [1.387, 2.08]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.867, 1.3], [1.305, 1.958], [0.203, 0.305], [0.836, 1.253]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.763, 1.145], [0.173, 0.259], [0.935, 1.403], [0.29, 0.434]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.472, 0.708], [0.505, 0.757], [0.811, 1.217], [0.936, 1.404]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.066, -0.099], [0.86, 1.29], [-0.13, -0.196], [1.285, 1.927]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.059, -0.089], [-0.69, -1.035], [-0.503, -0.754], [0.786, 1.18]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.302, 0.453], [0.535, 0.802], [0.708, 1.062], [-0.032, -0.049]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.167, 0.251], [0.167, 0.251], [0.97, 1.455], [0.63, 0.945]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.813, 1.22], [0.98, 1.47], [0.173, 0.259], [0.878, 1.317]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_359_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.185, -0.277], [0.661, 0.991], [0.877, 1.316], [-0.075, -0.112]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_361_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_361_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.142, 0.213], "wrong_answers": [[0.948, 1.422], [1.097, 1.646], [0.032, 0.048], [0.252, 0.378]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_361_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_361_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.876, 1.314], [0.233, 0.349], [0.81, 1.215], [1.093, 1.64]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_366_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_366_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.053, 1.579], [0.146, 0.219], [0.763, 1.145], [0.709, 1.063]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_366_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_366_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.013, 0.02], [-0.333, -0.499], [0.717, 1.076], [-0.115, -0.173]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_366_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_366_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.582, -0.873], [0.736, 1.104], [0.02, 0.031], [0.939, 1.408]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_366_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_366_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.735, 1.103], [-0.472, -0.708], [0.052, 0.078], [0.047, 0.071]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.061, 1.592], [0.114, 0.171], [-0.721, -1.081], [0.428, 0.641]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.82, 1.23], [0.735, 1.103], [1.013, 1.519], [0.965, 1.448]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.141, 1.711], [-0.121, -0.181], [0.081, 0.122], [0.153, 0.23]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.554, 0.832], [0.827, 1.24], [-0.265, -0.397], [0.064, 0.096]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.52, 0.781], [1.114, 1.671], [0.706, 1.06], [0.447, 0.67]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.238, -0.357], [0.106, 0.159], [0.822, 1.234], [0.27, 0.405]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.873, 1.31], [1.399, 2.098], [1.153, 1.729], [0.305, 0.458]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_371_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.034, 1.551], [0.712, 1.068], [0.763, 1.145], [1.497, 2.245]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.081, 1.622], [0.07, 0.105], [0.814, 1.22], [0.172, 0.258]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.737, 1.105], [-0.118, -0.177], [-0.197, -0.295], [0.143, 0.215]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_376_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_376_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.443, 0.664], [0.701, 1.051], [0.661, 0.991], [0.029, 0.043]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_376_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_376_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.971, 1.456], [-0.308, -0.462], [-0.204, -0.305], [0.155, 0.232]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_379_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_379_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.948, 1.422], [1.303, 1.955], [0.585, 0.877], [0.918, 1.377]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_379_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_379_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.631, 0.946], [0.465, 0.698], [0.914, 1.371], [0.541, 0.812]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.664, 0.995], [-0.089, -0.134], [-0.33, -0.495], [-0.102, -0.153]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.15, -0.225], [0.6, 0.9], [-0.067, -0.1], [-0.017, -0.025]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.124, 0.187], "wrong_answers": [[1.068, 1.603], [0.346, 0.519], [-0.037, -0.056], [0.36, 0.54]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_384_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.055, -0.083], [0.526, 0.788], [0.708, 1.063], [0.745, 1.118]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_387_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_387_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.255, 0.383], [0.119, 0.179], [1.554, 2.331], [1.093, 1.64]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_387_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_387_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.112, 1.669], [0.916, 1.374], [0.195, 0.293], [1.555, 2.332]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_389_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_389_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.537, 0.805], [0.505, 0.757], [0.567, 0.85], [-0.061, -0.091]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_389_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_389_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.086, -0.129], [0.992, 1.488], [0.017, 0.026], [-0.268, -0.403]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_390_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_390_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[1.499, 2.248], [0.106, 0.158], [-0.264, -0.396], [0.18, 0.27]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_390_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_390_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.603, 0.904], [0.11, 0.166], [-0.318, -0.477], [0.486, 0.729]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_391_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_391_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[-0.187, -0.281], [0.023, 0.034], [0.448, 0.672], [0.019, 0.029]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_391_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_391_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.622, 0.933], "wrong_answers": [[1.372, 2.058], [0.314, 0.471], [0.097, 0.145], [0.062, 0.092]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_392_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_392_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.884, 1.326], [1.102, 1.652], [0.804, 1.207], [0.241, 0.361]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_392_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_392_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.084, 0.126], [1.116, 1.674], [0.058, 0.087], [0.853, 1.279]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_395_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_395_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.806, 1.209], [0.866, 1.3], [0.213, 0.319], [-0.058, -0.086]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_395_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_395_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[1.348, 2.022], [0.721, 1.081], [0.006, 0.009], [0.244, 0.365]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_397_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_397_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.742, 1.113], [0.787, 1.18], [0.674, 1.01], [0.15, 0.225]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_397_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_397_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.018, 0.026], [-0.481, -0.722], [1.101, 1.652], [0.958, 1.436]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[1.351, 2.027], [1.264, 1.897], [1.164, 1.746], [-0.011, -0.016]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.045, 0.068], [0.171, 0.256], [-0.22, -0.33], [0.695, 1.042]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.169, -0.253], [0.733, 1.099], [-0.048, -0.072], [0.147, 0.22]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_398_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.429, -0.643], [-0.043, -0.065], [0.055, 0.083], [1.059, 1.588]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_400_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_400_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.092, 0.137], [0.457, 0.685], [1.147, 1.72], [1.052, 1.578]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_400_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_400_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.807, 1.211], [0.16, 0.24], [1.122, 1.684], [-0.076, -0.115]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_403_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_403_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.795, 1.193], [0.051, 0.077], [0.146, 0.219], [0.151, 0.227]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_403_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_403_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.973, 1.46], [1.292, 1.938], [1.215, 1.823], [1.015, 1.523]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_404_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_404_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.087, -0.131], [0.675, 1.012], [0.969, 1.453], [-0.186, -0.279]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_404_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_404_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.116, -0.174], [0.125, 0.188], [0.876, 1.315], [-0.534, -0.8]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_405_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_405_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.929, 1.393], [1.001, 1.502], [0.443, 0.665], [0.452, 0.678]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_405_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_405_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.71, 1.065], [0.857, 1.286], [-0.684, -1.025], [-0.169, -0.254]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_407_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_407_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.937, 1.406], [1.085, 1.628], [0.574, 0.861], [0.752, 1.128]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_407_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_407_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.124, 0.186], [0.215, 0.322], [0.985, 1.478], [-0.227, -0.341]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_407_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_407_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[-0.361, -0.541], [0.133, 0.2], [0.991, 1.486], [0.219, 0.328]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_407_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_407_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.158, -0.237], [0.065, 0.098], [0.423, 0.635], [0.79, 1.185]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_408_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_408_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.046, -0.069], [0.828, 1.242], [0.867, 1.3], [0.089, 0.134]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_408_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_408_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.618, 0.927], [-0.546, -0.818], [-0.475, -0.712], [0.517, 0.776]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_409_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_409_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.46, -0.69], [-0.265, -0.398], [1.037, 1.556], [0.748, 1.122]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_409_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_409_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.676, 1.013], [1.295, 1.942], [1.175, 1.762], [0.582, 0.873]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.079, 0.119], [0.555, 0.833], [0.063, 0.095], [0.635, 0.952]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.165, -0.248], [0.501, 0.751], [0.197, 0.296], [0.052, 0.077]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.504, 0.756], [0.067, 0.1], [1.117, 1.676], [-0.182, -0.273]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.64, 0.96], [0.706, 1.059], [-0.24, -0.36], [1.049, 1.574]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_411_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_411_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.852, 1.278], [0.16, 0.24], [0.144, 0.216], [1.401, 2.101]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_411_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_411_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.628, 0.943], [-0.276, -0.414], [0.588, 0.882], [0.567, 0.851]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_411_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_411_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[1.25, 1.875], [0.845, 1.268], [-0.145, -0.218], [0.828, 1.242]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_411_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_411_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.847, 1.27], [0.171, 0.257], [1.42, 2.131], [0.58, 0.87]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_415_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_415_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.857, 1.285], [0.659, 0.988], [0.736, 1.105], [0.084, 0.125]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_415_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_415_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.224, 0.336], [0.019, 0.029], [0.679, 1.018], [0.811, 1.216]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_416_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_416_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.914, -1.371], [0.723, 1.085], [-0.167, -0.251], [1.373, 2.06]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_416_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_416_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.118, -0.177], [0.825, 1.237], [0.885, 1.327], [0.103, 0.154]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_421_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_421_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.084, 0.125], [1.093, 1.64], [0.682, 1.023], [0.57, 0.855]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_421_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_421_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.102, 1.654], [-0.042, -0.064], [0.797, 1.195], [0.872, 1.308]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_423_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_423_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.105, 0.158], [0.825, 1.237], [0.612, 0.918], [-0.095, -0.142]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_423_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_423_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.666, 0.999], [-0.131, -0.197], [0.581, 0.871], [1.08, 1.621]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_424_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_424_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.896, 1.344], [0.028, 0.042], [0.032, 0.048], [-0.135, -0.202]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_424_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_424_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.689, 1.033], [0.713, 1.07], [0.148, 0.222], [-0.053, -0.08]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_428_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_428_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.991, 1.487], [0.949, 1.423], [0.23, 0.345], [0.816, 1.224]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_428_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_428_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.612, 0.917], [-0.36, -0.539], [0.746, 1.119], [0.202, 0.303]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_431_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_431_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.534, 0.801], [0.162, 0.243], [0.809, 1.213], [0.583, 0.874]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_431_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_431_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.681, -1.021], [-0.06, -0.09], [0.782, 1.173], [0.726, 1.088]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_433_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_433_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.893, 1.34], [0.605, 0.908], [0.674, 1.01], [0.885, 1.327]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_433_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_433_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.132, 1.698], [0.211, 0.316], [0.751, 1.127], [-0.074, -0.111]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_433_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_433_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.526, 0.789], [0.587, 0.88], [1.231, 1.847], [0.17, 0.254]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_433_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_433_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.721, 1.082], [0.807, 1.21], [0.015, 0.022], [-0.108, -0.162]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.881, 1.322], [0.174, 0.261], [0.735, 1.103], [-0.058, -0.087]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.093, 0.139], [0.506, 0.759], [-0.351, -0.527], [-0.309, -0.464]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.656, 0.984], [-0.251, -0.376], [0.76, 1.141], [0.689, 1.034]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_437_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.842, 1.263], [-0.236, -0.354], [1.015, 1.522], [-0.068, -0.102]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_439_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_439_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.008, 0.012], [0.866, 1.299], [-0.226, -0.339], [-0.142, -0.213]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_439_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_439_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[-0.048, -0.072], [0.307, 0.461], [0.365, 0.548], [0.379, 0.569]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_441_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_441_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.089, 0.134], [-0.163, -0.244], [0.943, 1.414], [1.399, 2.098]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_441_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_441_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.169, 0.254], [0.769, 1.153], [-0.019, -0.029], [0.147, 0.221]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.817, 1.225], [0.164, 0.246], [0.035, 0.052], [0.899, 1.348]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.446, 0.669], [0.414, 0.621], [0.385, 0.577], [0.062, 0.092]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.858, 1.288], [0.514, 0.771], [-0.039, -0.058], [0.661, 0.992]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_442_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.127, 0.191], [-0.036, -0.054], [0.683, 1.025], [0.531, 0.796]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_443_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_443_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.873, 1.31], [0.991, 1.486], [0.515, 0.773], [-0.281, -0.422]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_443_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_443_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.07, -0.105], [-0.028, -0.042], [0.121, 0.181], [0.151, 0.226]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_450_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_450_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.357, -0.536], [0.357, 0.536], [0.017, 0.026], [0.67, 1.005]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_450_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_450_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.78, 1.169], [0.17, 0.255], [1.161, 1.741], [0.758, 1.137]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_452_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_452_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.2, -0.3], [-0.232, -0.348], [-0.306, -0.459], [-0.206, -0.309]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_452_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_452_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.802, 1.203], [-0.108, -0.161], [0.212, 0.318], [0.651, 0.976]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_454_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_454_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.149, -0.223], [0.037, 0.056], [0.667, 1.0], [0.649, 0.974]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_454_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_454_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.121, -0.182], [0.539, 0.808], [0.626, 0.939], [0.182, 0.273]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_454_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_454_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.605, 0.908], [1.178, 1.767], [0.797, 1.195], [0.943, 1.415]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_454_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_454_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[-0.108, -0.162], [0.763, 1.145], [0.184, 0.277], [1.161, 1.742]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_456_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_456_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.764, 1.146], [0.287, 0.431], [1.651, 2.477], [-0.328, -0.492]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_456_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_456_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.063, 0.095], [-0.117, -0.176], [0.052, 0.077], [0.69, 1.036]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_459_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_459_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[1.136, 1.704], [0.024, 0.035], [-0.451, -0.676], [0.822, 1.233]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_459_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_459_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[-0.176, -0.263], [0.829, 1.244], [0.032, 0.048], [1.399, 2.098]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_468_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_468_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.622, 0.933], "wrong_answers": [[1.292, 1.937], [0.971, 1.457], [0.968, 1.451], [1.207, 1.81]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_468_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_468_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[0.223, 0.335], [0.173, 0.26], [0.902, 1.353], [0.338, 0.506]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_469_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_469_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[1.094, 1.642], [1.116, 1.674], [1.113, 1.67], [-0.157, -0.236]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_469_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_469_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.743, 1.115], [0.205, 0.307], [-0.071, -0.106], [0.778, 1.167]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.175, 0.263], [0.961, 1.442], [-0.389, -0.583], [0.205, 0.308]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.693, 1.039], [0.079, 0.119], [-0.07, -0.105], [0.13, 0.195]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.139, -0.209], [-0.428, -0.642], [-0.119, -0.178], [0.367, 0.55]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_470_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.464, 0.696], [0.316, 0.474], [0.129, 0.193], [-0.346, -0.518]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_471_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_471_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.881, -1.322], [-0.594, -0.891], [0.451, 0.676], [0.474, 0.711]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_471_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_471_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.495, 0.742], [0.504, 0.756], [0.553, 0.829], [-0.704, -1.056]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_477_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_477_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.49, 0.735], [0.369, 0.554], [0.054, 0.081], [0.84, 1.26]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_477_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_477_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.872, 1.308], [0.588, 0.881], [0.568, 0.851], [-0.012, -0.018]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_479_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_479_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.106, -0.16], [0.47, 0.704], [-0.254, -0.381], [0.008, 0.011]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_479_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_479_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[0.196, 0.294], [0.837, 1.255], [0.057, 0.086], [0.924, 1.386]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.018, -0.028], [0.3, 0.45], [0.221, 0.332], [0.149, 0.223]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.838, -1.257], [0.311, 0.467], [0.99, 1.486], [0.498, 0.747]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[0.799, 1.198], [0.425, 0.638], [0.328, 0.492], [0.799, 1.198]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.732, 1.098], [0.067, 0.1], [0.041, 0.062], [0.174, 0.26]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_483_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_483_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.578, 0.866], [-0.423, -0.635], [1.159, 1.739], [0.709, 1.063]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_483_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_483_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.692, 1.038], [0.01, 0.015], [0.772, 1.158], [0.028, 0.042]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_483_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_483_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.505, 0.757], [-0.314, -0.471], [0.098, 0.146], [0.136, 0.204]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_483_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_483_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.047, -0.07], [0.056, 0.084], [0.062, 0.093], [-0.402, -0.603]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_484_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_484_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.383, -0.575], [0.251, 0.376], [0.635, 0.953], [0.151, 0.227]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_484_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_484_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.432, 0.648], [0.96, 1.439], [0.503, 0.755], [0.445, 0.668]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_490_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_490_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.636, 0.953], [0.781, 1.172], [-0.1, -0.15], [-0.138, -0.208]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_490_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_490_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[1.181, 1.771], [0.943, 1.414], [0.84, 1.26], [-0.056, -0.084]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_491_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_491_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.604, 0.907], "wrong_answers": [[1.985, 2.977], [-0.237, -0.356], [0.271, 0.406], [1.238, 1.856]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_491_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_491_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.262, 0.394], [0.767, 1.15], [0.826, 1.239], [-0.184, -0.276]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_491_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_491_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.067, 1.6], [0.284, 0.426], [0.998, 1.497], [1.016, 1.524]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_491_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_491_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.867, 1.3], [-0.006, -0.008], [0.572, 0.858], [0.032, 0.047]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_492_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_492_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.344, -0.516], [0.463, 0.695], [0.747, 1.121], [0.865, 1.297]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_492_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_492_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.545, 0.818], [0.594, 0.891], [-0.116, -0.174], [-0.277, -0.415]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.654, 0.981], [0.809, 1.214], [-0.434, -0.652], [0.309, 0.464]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.569, 0.853], "wrong_answers": [[0.292, 0.438], [1.18, 1.77], [1.2, 1.8], [0.131, 0.196]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.894, 1.34], [0.799, 1.198], [0.289, 0.434], [0.813, 1.22]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_493_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.863, 1.294], [0.441, 0.661], [-0.325, -0.488], [0.021, 0.032]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_494_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_494_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.114, -0.172], [0.645, 0.968], [0.745, 1.118], [0.951, 1.426]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_494_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_494_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.648, 0.972], [-0.011, -0.016], [0.607, 0.91], [-0.002, -0.003]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_495_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_495_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.181, -0.272], [0.91, 1.365], [-0.017, -0.025], [0.489, 0.733]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_495_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_495_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.832, 1.249], [0.277, 0.415], [0.028, 0.041], [0.851, 1.277]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_497_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_497_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.054, 1.581], [1.124, 1.686], [0.744, 1.116], [0.736, 1.104]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_497_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_497_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.656, 2.484], [1.43, 2.144], [1.276, 1.914], [1.054, 1.581]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_497_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_497_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.022, 1.533], [0.182, 0.273], [0.299, 0.449], [1.189, 1.783]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_497_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_497_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.207, 0.31], [1.052, 1.578], [0.106, 0.159], [0.892, 1.338]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.195, 0.293], [0.036, 0.053], [0.681, 1.022], [1.125, 1.688]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.947, 1.421], [0.924, 1.385], [1.341, 2.012], [0.877, 1.315]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.242, 0.363], [0.834, 1.251], [-0.196, -0.294], [0.207, 0.31]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_498_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.252, 0.378], [0.204, 0.306], [0.106, 0.16], [0.077, 0.115]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_499_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_499_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.685, 1.028], [1.101, 1.652], [0.262, 0.393], [0.819, 1.229]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_499_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_499_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.2, 0.3], [-0.128, -0.191], [0.658, 0.987], [-0.217, -0.326]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_502_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_502_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.955, 1.432], [0.928, 1.391], [0.012, 0.017], [0.524, 0.786]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_502_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_502_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.086, 0.129], [-0.049, -0.074], [-0.292, -0.438], [0.002, 0.004]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_503_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_503_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.109, -0.163], [0.494, 0.741], [0.843, 1.264], [0.127, 0.191]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_503_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_503_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[-0.153, -0.23], [0.168, 0.252], [0.705, 1.058], [0.906, 1.358]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_504_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_504_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[1.104, 1.656], [0.873, 1.309], [0.988, 1.482], [0.188, 0.282]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_504_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_504_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.787, 1.181], [0.658, 0.987], [0.93, 1.395], [0.959, 1.438]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_506_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_506_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.737, 1.105], [0.184, 0.276], [0.458, 0.687], [0.565, 0.848]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_506_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_506_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.879, 1.319], [0.939, 1.409], [0.565, 0.848], [1.014, 1.521]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.646, 0.968], [0.091, 0.136], [-0.145, -0.217], [0.074, 0.112]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.071, -0.107], [-0.015, -0.022], [0.624, 0.936], [-0.091, -0.137]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.123, -0.185], [0.557, 0.835], [0.819, 1.228], [0.464, 0.696]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_509_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.131, 0.196], [1.594, 2.392], [-0.417, -0.626], [0.031, 0.046]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_509_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_509_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.239, 0.358], [0.999, 1.498], [0.205, 0.308], [0.323, 0.484]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_509_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_509_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.11, 0.166], [0.351, 0.527], [-0.183, -0.275], [0.081, 0.121]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_511_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_511_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.642, 0.964], [0.573, 0.859], [0.661, 0.992], [-0.14, -0.21]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_511_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_511_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.81, 1.216], [0.097, 0.146], [-0.301, -0.452], [0.829, 1.244]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_512_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_512_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.515, 0.772], [0.899, 1.349], [1.029, 1.544], [0.224, 0.335]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_512_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_512_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.939, 1.408], [0.013, 0.019], [-0.65, -0.975], [0.605, 0.908]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_513_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_513_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.598, 0.898], [0.495, 0.742], [0.558, 0.836], [0.693, 1.039]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_513_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_513_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.473, -0.709], [-0.378, -0.567], [0.648, 0.972], [0.927, 1.391]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_514_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_514_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.445, 0.667], [0.154, 0.23], [0.165, 0.248], [0.498, 0.747]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_514_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_514_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.25, -0.375], [-0.669, -1.004], [-0.021, -0.031], [0.349, 0.524]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_516_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_516_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.306, -0.459], [0.58, 0.869], [1.028, 1.542], [0.452, 0.678]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_516_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_516_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.206, 0.309], [1.212, 1.818], [0.684, 1.026], [0.91, 1.366]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_518_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_518_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[1.458, 2.187], [0.798, 1.197], [1.215, 1.823], [1.211, 1.816]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_518_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_518_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.978, 1.467], [0.037, 0.056], [-0.374, -0.561], [0.84, 1.259]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_519_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_519_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[1.46, 2.19], [1.137, 1.705], [-0.107, -0.16], [0.672, 1.009]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_519_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_519_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.178, -0.266], [0.656, 0.984], [1.222, 1.834], [0.134, 0.201]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.516, 0.773], [1.053, 1.579], [0.459, 0.688], [-0.232, -0.348]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.045, -0.067], [0.128, 0.193], [0.665, 0.998], [0.798, 1.197]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.105, -0.157], [0.358, 0.537], [1.186, 1.779], [0.819, 1.228]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_520_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.756, 1.134], [0.257, 0.385], [0.82, 1.23], [-0.219, -0.328]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_520_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_520_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.233, 0.349], [0.671, 1.006], [0.916, 1.374], [1.23, 1.846]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_520_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_520_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.089, 0.133], [0.599, 0.898], [0.621, 0.932], [0.501, 0.752]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_525_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_525_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.396, -0.594], [0.043, 0.064], [1.149, 1.723], [0.15, 0.225]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_525_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_525_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.609, 0.914], [1.097, 1.646], [0.242, 0.363], [1.079, 1.619]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_528_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_528_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.829, 1.243], [1.181, 1.771], [0.098, 0.147], [0.881, 1.321]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_528_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_528_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.595, 0.893], [0.661, 0.991], [0.18, 0.27], [0.894, 1.341]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_529_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_529_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.679, 1.018], [0.005, 0.007], [0.518, 0.777], [0.978, 1.467]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_529_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_529_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[1.035, 1.553], [1.242, 1.863], [0.299, 0.449], [0.797, 1.196]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_532_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_532_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.222, 0.333], [0.005, 0.008], [-0.265, -0.398], [0.087, 0.13]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_532_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_532_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.91, 1.365], [0.9, 1.35], [1.096, 1.643], [0.711, 1.067]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_532_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_532_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[-0.023, -0.035], [-0.023, -0.035], [0.225, 0.338], [0.004, 0.005]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_532_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_532_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.236, -0.355], [0.07, 0.105], [0.684, 1.026], [-0.09, -0.134]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_536_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_536_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[1.114, 1.671], [-0.287, -0.43], [1.145, 1.717], [1.247, 1.87]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_536_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_536_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.634, 0.951], [0.975, 1.463], [0.796, 1.195], [0.064, 0.096]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_538_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_538_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.322, -0.483], [0.096, 0.144], [-0.012, -0.018], [0.029, 0.043]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_538_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_538_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.09, 0.135], [0.022, 0.033], [0.495, 0.743], [0.091, 0.136]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.578, 0.868], [-0.108, -0.161], [-0.487, -0.73], [0.791, 1.187]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.816, 1.224], [0.885, 1.328], [0.188, 0.282], [0.273, 0.409]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.622, 0.933], "wrong_answers": [[-0.267, -0.4], [1.401, 2.101], [0.177, 0.265], [2.226, 3.338]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_540_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.602, 0.903], [-0.209, -0.314], [0.781, 1.171], [-0.22, -0.329]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_542_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_542_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[1.041, 1.561], [0.312, 0.467], [0.044, 0.066], [-0.109, -0.164]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_542_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_542_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.856, 1.283], [0.147, 0.221], [0.68, 1.02], [1.222, 1.833]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_543_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_543_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.664, 0.996], [1.199, 1.798], [0.999, 1.499], [0.056, 0.084]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_543_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_543_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.05, -0.075], [0.083, 0.125], [-0.222, -0.333], [0.092, 0.138]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_545_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_545_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.598, 0.897], [-0.215, -0.322], [0.074, 0.111], [0.005, 0.008]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_545_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_545_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[1.048, 1.572], [1.31, 1.965], [0.28, 0.42], [1.528, 2.292]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_545_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_545_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.188, 0.281], [0.972, 1.458], [1.254, 1.881], [0.861, 1.292]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_545_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_545_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.333, -0.499], [-0.244, -0.366], [0.07, 0.105], [1.111, 1.666]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.7, 1.05], [0.961, 1.441], [0.801, 1.201], [0.082, 0.122]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.217, -0.325], [0.66, 0.99], [0.781, 1.172], [0.085, 0.128]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[-0.059, -0.089], [-0.224, -0.335], [0.382, 0.573], [0.844, 1.267]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_546_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.682, 1.023], [0.716, 1.074], [0.147, 0.22], [-0.348, -0.522]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_553_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_553_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[-0.199, -0.298], [0.919, 1.378], [1.239, 1.859], [0.015, 0.022]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_553_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_553_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.056, 0.084], [0.544, 0.816], [0.047, 0.071], [0.626, 0.94]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_554_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_554_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.093, 0.139], [0.106, 0.159], [0.587, 0.881], [0.099, 0.148]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_554_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_554_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[1.428, 2.142], [0.602, 0.904], [0.668, 1.002], [1.296, 1.945]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.181, 0.271], [0.666, 0.999], [1.025, 1.537], [0.853, 1.279]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.388, 0.582], [0.562, 0.843], [-0.112, -0.168], [0.48, 0.719]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.194, -0.291], [0.868, 1.303], [0.15, 0.226], [0.004, 0.006]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_561_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[-0.078, -0.117], [0.865, 1.298], [-0.212, -0.318], [-0.165, -0.247]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.118, 0.176], [0.702, 1.053], [1.007, 1.511], [0.726, 1.09]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.507, 0.761], [0.84, 1.26], [0.676, 1.015], [-0.096, -0.145]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.465, 0.698], [0.057, 0.086], [0.449, 0.673], [1.066, 1.599]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_563_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.565, 0.847], [-0.417, -0.625], [-0.681, -1.022], [1.144, 1.716]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_566_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_566_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.442, 0.663], [0.447, 0.67], [0.699, 1.049], [0.523, 0.784]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_566_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_566_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.928, 1.392], [0.043, 0.064], [0.543, 0.814], [0.125, 0.187]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_569_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_569_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.274, -0.411], [0.514, 0.771], [-0.065, -0.098], [0.545, 0.818]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_569_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_569_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[0.898, 1.347], [1.007, 1.51], [0.913, 1.37], [1.268, 1.902]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[-0.113, -0.17], [0.23, 0.345], [0.79, 1.185], [0.75, 1.125]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[1.022, 1.533], [0.965, 1.447], [0.739, 1.108], [0.289, 0.434]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.842, 1.263], [0.732, 1.098], [0.019, 0.029], [0.018, 0.027]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_577_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.809, 1.213], [-0.007, -0.01], [0.105, 0.157], [0.232, 0.349]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_578_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_578_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.005, -0.008], [0.408, 0.611], [0.613, 0.919], [0.465, 0.698]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_578_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_578_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.735, 1.102], [0.249, 0.374], [0.662, 0.993], [1.061, 1.591]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_583_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_583_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.526, 0.789], [0.523, 0.784], [-0.155, -0.232], [0.702, 1.053]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_583_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_583_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.113, 0.169], [0.631, 0.946], [-0.184, -0.275], [0.787, 1.181]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_585_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_585_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[0.42, 0.629], [0.505, 0.757], [0.631, 0.946], [0.471, 0.706]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_585_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_585_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.853, 1.279], [-0.344, -0.515], [0.275, 0.412], [0.737, 1.106]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_587_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_587_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.216, -0.323], [-0.115, -0.172], [0.579, 0.869], [0.102, 0.153]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_587_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_587_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.014, 0.02], [1.05, 1.574], [-0.088, -0.132], [0.051, 0.077]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_591_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_591_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.083, -0.125], [0.136, 0.204], [1.307, 1.961], [-0.084, -0.126]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_591_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_591_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.171, -0.257], [1.099, 1.648], [-0.064, -0.095], [1.075, 1.612]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_592_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_592_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[-0.054, -0.081], [0.929, 1.394], [0.259, 0.388], [0.905, 1.358]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_592_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_592_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.13, -0.195], [-0.117, -0.175], [0.516, 0.774], [0.02, 0.031]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_596_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_596_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.852, 1.279], [-0.104, -0.156], [-0.321, -0.481], [0.554, 0.83]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_596_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_596_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[1.433, 2.15], [0.828, 1.242], [0.844, 1.266], [0.894, 1.342]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_597_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_597_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.871, 1.307], [1.757, 2.636], [0.768, 1.151], [0.998, 1.496]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_597_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_597_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.067, -0.1], [0.921, 1.381], [1.037, 1.556], [0.808, 1.212]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_601_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_601_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.686, 1.029], [0.435, 0.652], [0.732, 1.099], [0.088, 0.132]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_601_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_601_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.105, 0.158], [0.478, 0.717], [0.498, 0.748], [0.541, 0.811]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_601_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_601_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.125, -0.187], [0.46, 0.689], [0.395, 0.592], [-0.206, -0.309]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_601_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_601_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.569, 0.853], "wrong_answers": [[0.279, 0.418], [1.063, 1.595], [1.238, 1.857], [0.015, 0.022]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_605_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_605_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.793, 1.19], [0.03, 0.045], [1.202, 1.802], [0.989, 1.483]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_605_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_605_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.071, 0.106], [0.53, 0.794], [0.66, 0.99], [0.08, 0.121]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_605_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_605_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.65, 0.975], [-0.092, -0.138], [0.654, 0.981], [0.163, 0.244]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_605_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_605_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.96, 1.441], [-0.199, -0.299], [-0.421, -0.632], [0.7, 1.051]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_608_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_608_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[0.569, 0.853], [-0.599, -0.899], [0.104, 0.157], [0.281, 0.421]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_608_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_608_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[1.446, 2.169], [-0.053, -0.079], [0.203, 0.304], [1.193, 1.789]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_610_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_610_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.269, 0.404], [0.121, 0.182], [0.015, 0.023], [0.87, 1.305]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_610_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_610_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.15, 0.225], [-0.157, -0.235], [1.007, 1.51], [0.613, 0.919]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_612_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_612_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.923, 1.384], [0.126, 0.19], [0.717, 1.075], [1.072, 1.608]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_612_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_612_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.09, 0.135], [-0.069, -0.103], [-0.027, -0.041], [0.66, 0.99]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.799, 1.199], [0.588, 0.883], [0.799, 1.198], [0.476, 0.714]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[1.013, 1.519], [0.234, 0.351], [0.984, 1.476], [1.652, 2.478]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.903, 1.355], [-0.231, -0.346], [0.271, 0.406], [0.294, 0.441]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_614_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.142, 0.213], "wrong_answers": [[0.277, 0.416], [0.291, 0.436], [-0.117, -0.176], [0.643, 0.964]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_615_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_615_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.77, 1.155], [0.666, 1.0], [-0.29, -0.435], [0.778, 1.167]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_615_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_615_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.215, -0.323], [0.128, 0.191], [0.827, 1.24], [-0.182, -0.273]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_618_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_618_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.014, -0.021], [0.114, 0.171], [-0.262, -0.393], [1.031, 1.546]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_618_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_618_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.077, 0.116], [0.025, 0.038], [0.03, 0.046], [-0.425, -0.638]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_619_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_619_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.613, 0.92], [0.77, 1.155], [0.865, 1.297], [0.569, 0.853]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_619_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_619_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.591, 0.886], [0.58, 0.87], [0.568, 0.853], [0.97, 1.455]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.802, 1.203], [0.037, 0.055], [0.787, 1.18], [1.516, 2.274]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.842, -1.264], [0.417, 0.625], [0.075, 0.113], [-0.042, -0.063]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.124, 0.187], "wrong_answers": [[-0.239, -0.358], [-0.374, -0.562], [-0.151, -0.227], [0.357, 0.535]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.979, 1.469], [0.83, 1.245], [1.053, 1.579], [0.268, 0.403]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_622_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_622_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.319, 1.978], [0.962, 1.442], [-0.26, -0.389], [0.019, 0.029]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_622_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_622_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.538, 0.806], [0.93, 1.395], [0.927, 1.39], [0.953, 1.429]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.031, 0.047], [1.405, 2.108], [0.123, 0.184], [0.603, 0.905]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.091, -0.137], [0.16, 0.24], [0.802, 1.203], [0.479, 0.718]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.975, 1.463], [0.6, 0.901], [0.458, 0.687], [0.532, 0.798]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_623_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.738, 1.107], [1.019, 1.529], [0.722, 1.082], [0.438, 0.657]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_624_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_624_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.007, 0.011], [0.135, 0.202], [0.943, 1.414], [-0.263, -0.395]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_624_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_624_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[1.248, 1.872], [0.989, 1.483], [0.004, 0.006], [0.583, 0.874]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.679, 1.019], [-0.185, -0.278], [-0.607, -0.91], [0.35, 0.526]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.176, 0.264], [0.553, 0.83], [-0.163, -0.244], [0.77, 1.155]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_626_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_626_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.451, 0.676], [0.51, 0.764], [0.61, 0.914], [1.237, 1.855]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_626_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_626_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.718, -1.076], [0.537, 0.806], [-0.086, -0.129], [0.022, 0.033]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_630_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_630_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.429, -0.644], [0.763, 1.145], [-0.08, -0.12], [0.152, 0.228]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_630_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_630_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.606, 0.908], [0.05, 0.074], [0.129, 0.193], [-0.292, -0.438]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_631_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_631_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[1.286, 1.929], [-0.933, -1.399], [0.959, 1.438], [-0.1, -0.149]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_631_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_631_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.798, 1.197], [0.762, 1.143], [0.608, 0.911], [0.085, 0.127]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_639_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_639_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.061, 0.091], [0.713, 1.069], [-0.388, -0.583], [0.048, 0.072]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_639_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_639_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[-0.044, -0.066], [0.183, 0.274], [0.956, 1.434], [1.146, 1.719]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_641_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_641_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.315, 0.473], [0.317, 0.475], [0.131, 0.197], [0.069, 0.104]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_641_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_641_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[0.014, 0.02], [0.087, 0.131], [-0.319, -0.478], [0.545, 0.818]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_644_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_644_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.111, -0.166], [-0.551, -0.826], [0.527, 0.791], [0.748, 1.122]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_644_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_644_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.289, 0.433], [-0.458, -0.687], [0.099, 0.149], [-0.381, -0.572]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_646_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_646_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.407, 0.611], [-0.165, -0.247], [1.203, 1.804], [0.438, 0.657]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_646_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_646_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[-0.332, -0.497], [-0.01, -0.015], [1.128, 1.691], [0.251, 0.377]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_647_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_647_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.951, 1.426], [-0.213, -0.319], [0.92, 1.379], [0.581, 0.871]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_647_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_647_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.07, 0.105], [1.186, 1.779], [0.152, 0.228], [-0.054, -0.08]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.138, 0.206], [-0.32, -0.481], [0.687, 1.03], [0.103, 0.154]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.006, -0.008], [0.161, 0.242], [-0.142, -0.214], [-0.091, -0.136]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.44, 0.66], [-0.18, -0.271], [0.887, 1.331], [0.028, 0.043]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.271, -0.406], [0.589, 0.883], [0.749, 1.124], [0.795, 1.192]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.058, -0.088], [0.66, 0.99], [0.391, 0.586], [1.063, 1.594]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.328, 1.991], [0.719, 1.078], [0.959, 1.439], [-0.049, -0.073]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_653_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_653_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.084, 0.126], [1.038, 1.557], [0.169, 0.254], [0.172, 0.258]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_653_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_653_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.081, 0.122], [0.564, 0.846], [-0.456, -0.684], [-0.094, -0.142]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_654_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_654_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.095, -0.142], [0.541, 0.811], [1.474, 2.211], [0.95, 1.425]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_654_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_654_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.146, 0.219], [0.881, 1.321], [0.19, 0.286], [0.09, 0.134]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_657_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_657_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.006, 0.009], [-0.115, -0.172], [-0.114, -0.17], [0.949, 1.423]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_657_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_657_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.959, 1.439], [0.921, 1.381], [0.22, 0.33], [-0.109, -0.163]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_659_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_659_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.631, 0.946], [0.114, 0.172], [-0.208, -0.313], [1.083, 1.625]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_659_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_659_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.542, 0.813], [0.008, 0.012], [-0.19, -0.285], [-0.198, -0.297]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.195, 1.792], [0.635, 0.952], [0.611, 0.917], [-0.454, -0.681]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[1.005, 1.508], [0.318, 0.476], [0.959, 1.439], [0.252, 0.378]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_661_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_661_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.329, 0.493], [0.883, 1.325], [0.221, 0.332], [0.791, 1.187]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_661_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_661_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.661, 0.992], [0.676, 1.015], [0.437, 0.656], [0.607, 0.91]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_665_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_665_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.418, 0.628], [0.553, 0.829], [0.554, 0.831], [0.52, 0.78]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_665_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_665_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.429, 0.643], [0.169, 0.253], [0.038, 0.057], [0.487, 0.731]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.012, 1.518], [0.727, 1.091], [1.194, 1.792], [0.698, 1.047]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.629, 0.943], [0.851, 1.277], [0.436, 0.654], [0.911, 1.367]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.778, 1.167], [0.012, 0.018], [0.856, 1.284], [0.766, 1.149]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_681_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.147, 0.22], [-0.054, -0.08], [0.503, 0.755], [0.079, 0.119]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_682_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_682_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[-0.039, -0.058], [0.911, 1.366], [0.68, 1.02], [1.171, 1.757]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_682_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_682_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.65, 0.974], [0.029, 0.044], [-0.097, -0.146], [-0.01, -0.015]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_682_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_682_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.932, 1.399], [0.02, 0.029], [0.92, 1.38], [0.132, 0.198]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_682_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_682_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.246, -0.369], [-0.206, -0.309], [0.859, 1.288], [-0.349, -0.523]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_683_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_683_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.912, 1.368], [0.852, 1.278], [-0.363, -0.545], [1.354, 2.031]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_683_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_683_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.604, 0.907], "wrong_answers": [[0.251, 0.376], [0.908, 1.362], [0.379, 0.569], [0.247, 0.371]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_687_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_687_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[0.914, 1.372], [1.179, 1.768], [1.059, 1.588], [1.316, 1.973]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_687_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_687_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.186, 0.279], [0.916, 1.374], [0.243, 0.365], [0.718, 1.077]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_689_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_689_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.689, 1.034], [0.733, 1.099], [-0.442, -0.663], [0.113, 0.17]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_689_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_689_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[-0.134, -0.2], [-0.137, -0.205], [0.109, 0.163], [0.502, 0.753]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_693_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_693_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[1.036, 1.555], [0.67, 1.004], [0.463, 0.694], [0.325, 0.487]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_693_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_693_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.013, -0.019], [0.629, 0.944], [0.409, 0.613], [0.435, 0.652]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_694_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_694_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.301, -0.452], [1.626, 2.44], [0.568, 0.852], [0.485, 0.727]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_694_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_694_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.023, -0.035], [-0.071, -0.106], [0.062, 0.093], [0.642, 0.963]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_697_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_697_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.405, 0.608], [0.363, 0.545], [-0.086, -0.129], [0.329, 0.494]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_697_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_697_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.664, 0.997], [-0.107, -0.16], [-0.173, -0.26], [0.491, 0.737]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_698_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_698_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.64, -0.96], [0.562, 0.842], [0.632, 0.948], [0.522, 0.783]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the accuracy of Logistic Regression ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_698_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_698_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}